007b.com 2012-10-28

# Privacy policy at www.007b.com

The privacy of our visitors is important to us. This policy provides you with information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit 007b.com. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

You may access and browse 007b.com without disclosing any of your personal information (such as name, address, telephone number, email address, or credit card information) nor do we collect information about our visitors from any public records. 

If you voluntarily submit your email address or other information to us, I may use that to contact you. 007b.com will not trade, sell or share your personal information that you voluntarily submit to us to any third party. 

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do not use any cookies on 007b.com.

We do use third party advertisements on 007b.com to support our site, notably Google Adsense and Amazon ads. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information about your IP address, your ISP, your browser, whether you have Flash installed, and about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. This information is not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off the third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. You may may opt out of the use of Google's DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

To see Amazon's and Google's privacy policies, click here: [Amazon.com Privacy Notice](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/browse/-/468496/102-6533223-3461729) or [Google Ads Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).   

* * *

_Please[contact us](http://www.007b.com/contact.php) if you have further questions._
